To be continued...
Spirits are not human beings.
And human beings are certainly not spirits.
Even though they have some similarities, their differences abound.
Poor Shido.
He's far more than slightly confused.
Spirits are not human beings.
Spirits are human beings.
A love of love.
you
Now then, how about you and I engage in a little bit of spirited competition?
Is this really the best you can do? I have to say I'm unimpressed.
You can call forth an angel and command flame. Surely you can be below me, can't you?
Oh well, guess not!
Why don't you keep your mouth shut? You're a lot cuter when you're not talking!
Well, I happen to think you would be a lot cuter with your pretty little head mounted on my wall!
Zavkiel! Zayun!
Zay, stop it! Please!
It must really suck to be you right now. Frozen in time and completely surrounded.
Oh well. Bye-bye, flame girl.
A point-blank shot to the noggin.
That'll sure dampen your spirit, eh?
It really is too bad. I was actually starting to enjoy her.
And now she's dead.
Now that that's settled, you're on deck, Shido.
Let's have a little fun.
Monologuing always gets the bad guy in trouble.
Not part of your plan?
If you'd rather tuck your tail between your legs and run home to mommy, I'd completely understand.
Ha! Not in your wildest dreams, flame girl!
Ah!
Aleph!
What are you doing?
I've heard of pieces!
Come on!
Damn you!
Comes up kill!
Don't lie to hell!
Oh, come on! Don't give up on me already!
You can't quit just when your opponent is warmed up! It's bad form!
I promise you this.
You'll be sorry you ever decided to mess with me.
Soft kill!
Yeah! Show me what you got!
What's happening?
Kotari!
It looks like your devil's luck has run out!
Kotari! Are you alright?
Come, I'll...
Make it all!
Roll it to me immediately!
Turn them on to ashes!
Do it! Come on!
Pick up your weapon!
This fight's not over yet, and the war's not over yet either!
Well, come on then!
Let's have some more of that destruction you love so much!
This is the fight you wanted!
This is the war you wanted, isn't it?
If you can't face the muzzle of a gun anymore, it's over.
Time for you to die.
Kotari!
If you keep pushing like this, she will die!
Isn't the point of Ratatasker to resolve conflicts without killing spirits?
You have to stop!
Stay back!
No... don't... please...
Big Brother, look out!
Big Brother!
Would you like me to operate?
Yes, please.
Thank you, doctor.
All righty then!
Nurse, please hand me my scalpel!
Oh...
I was playing doctor.
Sorry.
You're fine.
Toka, she's here too?
Why am I in a sickbay?
Well, you're awake, that's good.
Looks like the anesthesia didn't work.
Good thing you woke up before I cut you open.
I really am sorry.
I hope I didn't scare you.
Please, I'm fine, really.
Hey, Reina, tell me, what am I doing in here?
The thing is, you were knocked out in the battle with Kurumi,
so we brought you here just to be on the safe side.
Yeah, yeah, that's right.
But I don't know what happened after that.
What about Toka? She's just sleeping, isn't she?
No, hey, where is Kotari? What was that power?
You need to calm down, Shin.
No, I'm not gonna calm down.
Wait, what about Kurumi?
And Mana, is she all right?
And everyone from school?
Everything will be just fine.
Do you feel better now?
Yeah.
Everybody is doing okay, and no one was killed.
All things considered, it could have been much worse.
As far as Origami and Mana,
they were both taken by members of the AST.
We can't be certain yet,
but our best guess is they were brought to Tengu Hospital.
Kurumi ran off while she had the chance,
and as you can see, Toka is sleeping.
Even though she's hurt, she wanted to be by your side.
Toka cares more about you than she does her own recovery.
Not to worry, though.
She's gonna be fine.
That's good.
But this isn't the end, is it?
Of course not.
Kotari, can I see her?
She can't hear or see us through the protective wall.
You're going to be on your own in there.
Hey, you.
I didn't expect to see you up and about.
How are you feeling?
Better, I guess.
What about you?
Are you feeling okay?
I feel like my normal, super cute self.
Not sure it's normal to call yourself cute.
You don't think I'm cute?
No.
You're right.
I guess you're kind of cute.
But, Kotari, tell me the truth.
Are you really your spirit?
Answer me.
Are you a spirit or not?
Well, if I told you that I wasn't a spirit, would you believe me?
Of course.
If you said so, then I would.
Is that right?
You'd believe what someone says, even when you've seen the contrary to be true?
If you want my two cents, that seems like a fast way to make a fool of yourself.
If I can't even trust my little sis, what kind of brother would that make me?
Look, I said I'd believe you.
I always will, no matter what.
I think I'm a human being.
I mean, I wouldn't call myself a spirit.
Although, the observation equipment might beg to differ.
I have no doubt the machine says I'm lying to you.
Wait, what do you mean?
I was born into the Itsuka family.
And that much I know for sure.
But five years ago, somehow I became a flame spirit.
That might not be the best way to put it.
I guess it's more accurate to say I became a person who possesses spirit powers.
Seriously?
This might sound nuts, but I knew about this.
That's impossible.
I never said anything to you.
No, no, that's not what I'm saying.
I had this dream.
Kotiri, no!
Big brother, big brother, no!
Big brother, I'm sorry, brother.
I have to say, I'm not sure I agree with the part where I was screaming out for you and crying like a big baby.
But more or less, that's the way I remember it, too.
It's possible it may have flowed to you through the path when the spirit powers returned to me.
I see.
But I still don't get it.
What happened?
How did you become a spirit?
I wish I could tell you, but the truth is I don't remember.
Huh?
I mean, obviously I know something must have happened back then, but for the life of me, I don't know what.
I remember becoming a spirit, but I don't know how, or even why for that matter.
How can you forget something so important?
Look who's talking.
You're in no position to pass judgment on the forgetful front, big bro.
Well, but then again, you're right.
It's kind of weird that neither of us has any memory of it all.
You'd think we would remember everything.
Who knows?
Maybe somebody erased our memories for some reason.
Well, it's a theory anyway.
After that, I was discovered by Rattatasker.
Then I found out the truth about what was going on behind the scenes,
and I decided I wanted to save the spirits.
But once you got past that big fire, you lived a pretty typical life.
How were you able to blend in with the regular kids?
What? You don't remember that part either?
I was able to be a normal girl because you sealed away my spirit powers.
Really? Wait, are you serious?
Yeah. Didn't I tell you yesterday?
Don't let me forget to give this back to you, Shido.
I don't fully understand why, but for some inexplicable reason,
you're able to seal away a spirit's power.
And that's why you were chosen by Rattatasker to talk to the spirits.
You're special, Shido.
So, my regeneration ability came from...
Yes, your ability came from mine!
Now, listen up.
Come over here and stand right in front of me.
Why should I do that?
Because I said so.
Fine.
I told you to be careful, didn't I?
But you didn't listen to me.
If I hadn't come to my senses, you'd be dead meat.
You're very lucky.
What the heck were you thinking anyway, you idiot?
Running out in front of my light in a fire like that?
You scared me.
I thought you'd lost it.
And I was right.
You weren't yourself.
Yeah.
When the spirit powers returned to me, I lost control.
All I wanted to do was break something.
Or better yet, kill someone if I got the chance.
I was scared.
It was like I was a different person.
Who knows what other awful things I've done that I have no memory of.
There's no telling if it's that easy for me to lose control over myself.
I wouldn't be shocked if I already have killed someone.
Stop talking like that!
Just ignore me.
I don't even know what I'm talking about.
But I do think I know why I snapped out of it yesterday.
It's because you stepped in front of me.
Thanks for saving the day, big bro.
About your spirit power.
Will it come back to me?
I don't really know.
Unfortunately, spirit stuff isn't always easy to understand.
All I know for sure is this.
You'll have to seal it just like you did before.
But to seal it away, I'd have to...
Yes, take me on a date and make me fall in love.
The same way you did with Toka and Yoshino.
You have to.
Hey!
Kotari?
Are you all right?
Can you stand?
Yeah, I'm okay.
You don't need to worry about me.
Please, talk to me.
Shin, that's enough for today, all right?
You go ahead.
I'll handle things from here.
No, I can't.
We'll have lots to discuss later.
But for now, go on.
Okay.
Shino, I've been looking everywhere.
I was worried, because when I woke up, you were gone.
But you're awake, so does this mean you're feeling better?
I don't know.
Do you mind if we talk later?
Yeah, okay.
I give her two days.
I doubt she'll last much longer than that.
Eventually, her spirit power will be too much for her to handle.
What do you mean by that?
Once the power overtakes her completely, Kotari will no longer be anything like the little
sister you once knew and loved.
In just under 48 hours, we'll have you go on a date with her.
That'll be your best chance to make sure she doesn't slip away forever.
Sorry, sir, but you're not allowed to see her.
Not even her family can do that yet.
I do apologize, but I'm afraid I don't know when she's going to be allowed visitors.
But why?
Is it really that bad?
I wish I could help, but unfortunately, at this time, I can't discuss her condition with you.
Ma'am, please.
Shido.
Origami.
I'm glad you're safe.
Is Toka okay?
Uh, yeah.
She's, uh, she's good.
Never mind.
So, you came here to see Mana, huh?
Yeah, well, I tried to, but the nurse wouldn't allow it.
I can't go into specifics, but for Mana's recovery, they're using some highly classified equipment on her.
So, until she's moved to the general ward, there's no way they'll let anyone see her.
And if you try to force your way in, it won't end well.
I know that's why you're here.
Huh?
To see Mana and nobody else.
Oh, well, obviously, I came to visit you, too.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, I'd better get a move on.
I'm sure you're really busy.
I bet you have lots of doctor's appointments and stuff like that.
Later.
Origami?
Are you all right?
I can't make it back to my room on my own.
Will you please carry me?
I should get a nurse.
Carry me right now.
Come on, who needs a nurse?
Can you walk?
No, I can't.
What you need is a wheelchair.
I'll get one.
No, please stop.
I can't handle that.
I'll vomit from motion sickness.
What do you expect me to do about it?
Take it back, me.
Huh?
You heard me.
Right.
Hey, Origami, don't you think you're holding on a little tight there?
Um, no.
You're in room 305 all the way in the west wing, aren't you?
Okay, that tickles.
Please, don't.
Man up.
Uh, Origami, stop.
Oh, boy.
All right, that's enough.
Hey, licking is crossing the line, okay?
Well, then, I'm just gonna go ahead and go.
Peel it.
Uh, well, I suppose I can make that happen.
Now feed it to me.
Don't you think this is getting a little crazy?
You wanna see crazy?
Try not feeding me.
Now put it in my...
Mine, here!
Ah!
Um, please stop.
Wait, don't stop.
No, do.
It's gross.
And awesome, too.
Oh, God.
Too much.
It's delicious.
Great.
I'm glad to hear you liked it.
So, anyway, I'm gonna take off now.
But what about my temperature?
I'm gonna need your help
sticking it in my mouth.
Oh, all right.
Fine.
Why am I sitting down to take your temperature?
This is inappropriate.
What the heck is going on?
Well, you seem to get excited by Kurumi's behavior.
Since you like that sort of thing,
I thought I'd turn up the volume and get more aggressive.
Here are the rules, big boy.
If you look, you have to touch.
Goodbye, Origami.
I'm really leaving this time.
Can I ask you one more thing?
It's important.
I want you to tell me what happened after the fight with Kurumi Tokisaki yesterday.
Because I thought I saw another spirit floating in the sky.
She was surrounded by flames.
Flames she could control.
Then I must have passed out.
The next thing I knew, I woke up in here.
So I want you to tell me what I missed.
No matter how insignificant the details,
I want to know everything that happened
and everything you know about this flame spirit.
Oh, well, uh...
I got knocked out too, so I don't know much.
Why do you ask?
Just curious.
Well, do you know her?
The flame spirit, I mean.
Yes, I do.
Five years ago, there was a massive fire in Tengu City.
It mainly broke out in a small neighborhood called Nanko.
And that's when I first saw her, the day she burned my parents alive.
Big Brother!
Ever since she killed my family, I've spent every waking moment searching for her.
No one should ever have to feel the way I felt that day.
She's the reason I joined the AST.
The reason I trained as hard as I could.
She's why I get out of bed in the morning,
and she's what I think about when I go to sleep.
I promised myself back then that when I had the chance, I wouldn't hesitate.
I'd wrap my hands around her throat,
look her in the eyes,
and crush every last bit of remaining life.
And now, my opportunity is right in front of me.
This is the moment I've been waiting for.
I swear to you,
I will kill the flame spirit.
There are people,
and they circle the flame spirit.
They are the best by the gift card.
Give up the craftsman,
and keep having fun.
It's no way.
place too much for you.
There's places you can say.
It's no way.
努力で走り続けるよ
また会えますか?
信じてくれますか?
恋に見てひらるもので
S.A.S.A. War
世界が終わる前に生きる大きい 君が笑ってくれたら嬉しいのです